海绵宝宝  之
过不完的夏天
翻译  1440kHz
到蟹堡王去上班
I'm off to work at the Krusty Krab
做蟹黄堡扯扯淡
fryin' up patties and blabbity bla-
蟹堡王
这倒新鲜
That's new
把车停到这也太怪了吧
Strange place to park a car
这是干嘛的
What's this for?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
你这是在浪费我的宝贝二氧化碳
You're wastin' me precious carbon dioxide
二氧化碳
Carbon dioxide?
我在把它排放到大气层  小子
I'm pumpin' it into the atmosphere, boy
全球气候变暖了
Thanks to global warmin'
所以说气温很快就会飞涨
the temperature will soon go through the roof
这样就能过上过不完的夏天了
and then we'll have an endless summer
干嘛想要个过不完的夏天  蟹老板
Why do you want an endless summer, Mr. Krabs?
这样就能开展我最新的赚钱大计
So I can open me latest money-makin' venture
蟹堡泳池
the Krusty Pool
可是冬季运动怎么办  蟹老板
But, what about winter sports, Mr. Krabs?
别管冬季了  小子
Forget winter, boy
重点可是晒日光浴  冲浪
We're talkin' sun tannin', hangin' 10
还有游泳一整年
and swimmin' all year long
过不完的夏天听着确实好玩
The endless summer does sound fun
还能赚大钱
And profitable
又好玩又能赚大钱
Fun and profitable
大生意又成功了
Big business does it again
真希望能马上就过上过不完的夏天
I just wish it could be the endless summer right now
雨伞三块钱  先生
Umbrellars are three dollars, sir
真实惠
What a bargain
我给你五块
I'll give ya five
怎么
What the--?
真见鬼
Barnacles
里面突然就热起来了
It suddenly got very warm in here
是谁调高了
Who turned up the--
暖气
heat?
海绵宝宝  你干什么
SpongeBob, what are ya doin'?
只是再往火堆里丢个轮胎进去
Just throwin' another tire on the fire
促进全球气候变暖  蟹老板
for global warming, Mr. Krabs
快看
Look
成功了
It's working
全裤头村都过来解暑了
The entire town is heading this way to cool off
也就是要来付我钱了
You mean pay off
快点  海绵宝宝
Hurry, SpongeBob
给泳池装水啊
Fill the pool, fill the pool
遵命  老板
Aye-aye, sir
把你们的钱都准备好吧
Have your money ready, folks
游泳
队伍从这里开始排
The line starts here
大家这是要去哪
Where's everybody goin'?
我们要搬去北方
We're all moving north
这里再也没法住了
We can't live here anymore
都快热死了
It's too hot
我客人都搬去气候更凉快的地方了
All me customers have moved to cooler climates
乐观点看嘛  蟹老板
Look on the bright side, Mr. Krabs
泳池不会有人来排队了
There won't be a line to go in the pool
炮来了
Cannonball